A Guide to the R. Bolling Batte Papers, 1918-1992
Library of Virginia
- Subject Files and County Research Notes (Box 22-33)
  - Buckingham Census (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - C - Correspondence - Misc. (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Campbell County - Census (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Campbell County - Marriages (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Campbell County Records (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Caroline County - Marriages (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Carter Tree - Original Pages (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - The Cemeteries of Leon County, Fla. (P-180) (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Census - Misc. (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Census Reports (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Census Reports - 2nd Copy (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Charles City County - Census (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Charles City County - Fleet Extracts (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Charles City County Loose Papers (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Charles City County Order Book, 1766-1774 - Extracts (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Charles City County Records (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Charles City County Tax Records (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Charlesworth, Mrs. Frances - Colonial Dames Application (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Charlotte County - Census (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Charlotte County - Field Work (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Charlotte County - Misc. Records (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Chesterfield County - Census (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Chesterfield County - Marriages (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - CW Times Index Card Project (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Clarke County - Census (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Clerical Directory (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Clippings - Batte (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Clippings - Marriages and Deaths (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Clippings - Misc. (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Colonial Dames (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Colonial Dames - Form Prints (RBB File) (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Colonial Dames - Mrs. Hardy (Preliminary Drafts) (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Confederate Veteran (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Congress - U.S. Biographical Directory (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Congressman Bolling Project (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1924, 1931, 1941 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1950-1959 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1960-1969 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1970-1979 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1980-1989 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence - Laurence B. Gardiner (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence - To Be Answered (Box 24, Folder 12-13)
  - Court Cases (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Culpeper County - Marriages (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Cumberland County - Census (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Cumberland County - Marriages (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Cumberland County - Misc. Records (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Debutantes (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Desk Calendar Sheets, 1980-1981 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Desk Calendar Sheets, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Dinwiddie County - Bath Parish Register (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Dinwiddie County - Census (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Dinwiddie County - Map, 1878 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Dinwiddie County - Marriages (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Dinwiddie County - Misc. Records (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Dinwiddie County Plat Book with Index (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Doctors (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Elizabeth City County - Census (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Episcopal Ministers (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Excerpts from Printed Lineage Books (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Excerpts from R.H. Batte's Book (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Extracts from Various Published Books (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Fauquier County - Marriages (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - For Work in VSL (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Franklin County Records (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Fredericksburg Marriage Bonds (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Gary, Tom C. - Correspondence (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Gary, Tom C. - Genealogical Correspondence (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Genealogical (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Genealogical Books (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - A Genealogical History by Col. Cadwallader Jones (P-142) (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Genealogies - J.P. Madison Notes (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Genealogy (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Genealogy - English Royal Line (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Genealogy Series in the Richmond Times-Dispatch, April 1977 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Gibson Correspondence (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Goochland County Census (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Goochland County Records (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Gravestone Inscriptions in Northampton County, Virginia (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Greensville County - Census (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Greensville County - Field Work - Emporia (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Greensville County - Marriages (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Greensville County Records (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Halifax County - Marriages (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Headrights (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Hampden-Sidney College Indexing Project (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Henrico County - Census (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Henrico County - Marriages (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Henrico County - Misc. Records, 1650-1807 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Henrico County Records (Box 26, Folder 21-22)
  - Henrico County Records - Extra Typed Copies (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Henrico County - Field Work (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Henrico County Records - Fleet (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Henry County - Marriages (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Heraldry (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Hever Castle (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Hiden - Adventurers of Purse and Person (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - James City County - Census (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Jamestowne Society (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - The Jones-Burgwin Family History (P-155) (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - The Jones Family by Lee Nicholson, 1920 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - King and Queen County - Historical Society Bulletin (July 1968) (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - King William County - Census (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Lancaster County - Marriages (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Land Survey Data (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Leon County, Florida (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Leon County, Florida - Houses (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Leon County, Florida Records (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Lunenburg County - Census (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Lunenburg County - Field Check (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Lunenburg County - Marriages (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Lunenburg County Records (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Lunenburg County - St. John's Church Tombstone Inscriptions (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Lynchburg - Marriages (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Manchester - Marriages (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Maps (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Marriages - Miscellaneous (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Maury, Elizabeth Bull - Misc. Genealogical Notes (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Mecklenburg County - Census (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Mecklenburg County - Marriage Bonds (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Mecklenburg County Records (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Mercer, Joseph M. - Correspondence (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Middlesex County Records (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Families (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Family Information (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Genealogical (Box 28, Folder 4-7)
  - Miscellaneous Notes - Ingram (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Monumental Church - List of Members (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Nansemond County Records (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper Extracts (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Nicholson - Batte (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Nicholson - Briggs (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Nicholson - Chappell (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Nicholson - Jones/Epes/Hardaway/Bland (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Nicholson - Mallory (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Nicholson - Mason/Parham (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Nicholson - Misc. Letters (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Nicholson - Parham/Branch (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Nicholson - Pegram/Scott/Parham (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Nicholson - Rives/Blow/Chamblis (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Norfolk City Census (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Norfolk City Records (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Norfolk County Census (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Norfolk County Records (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Norfolk Marriages (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Northumberland Census (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Northumberland Records (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Nottoway Census (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Nottoway Records (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Obituary Notices in Newspapers (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - On the Memorial Art of Tidewater Virginia, 1650-1775 by Patrick Henry Butler III (Master's Thesis) (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Orange County - General (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Orange County Marriages (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Parish Registers (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Pedigree Chart - Browder, Barbara (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Pedigree - Burwell/Armistead/Page/Nelson (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Pedigree Chart - Drummond, Frances Harrison (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Pedigree Chart - French, Eliza Bland (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Pedigree Chart - Graham, Margaret Etheredge (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Pedigree Chart - Jones, Robert Thomas (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Pedigree Chart - Pinner, Laura Etheredge (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Pedigree Charts - Miscellaneous (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Petersburg Census (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Petersburg Death Register (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Petersburg Marriages (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Petersburg Newspapers (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Misc. Petersburg Sources (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Photographs (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Pittsylvania Census (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Pittsylvania Marriages (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Pocahontas (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Powhatan County Census (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Prince Edward Census (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Prince Edward Marriages (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Prince George Census (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Prince George County Abstracts (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Prince George County Records (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Prince George Deed Books 18, 22, 24 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Prince George Marriages (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Prince George Order Book, 1811-1813 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Prince George Records, 1713-1728 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Prince George Records, 1737-1739 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Prince George Records, 1787-1792 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Prince George Records - Peebles Notes (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Prince George Surveys (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Prince George Tax Records (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Prince George Misc. County Records (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Princess Anne County Census (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Princess Anne Marriages (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Publications - Genealogical (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Quaker Records (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Randolph, William (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - References (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - The Religion of Robert Browning by Robert Bolling Batte IV (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Richmond City (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Richmond City Census (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Richmond County (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Richmond Enquirer Items (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - Richmond Hustings Court - Marriage Records - Field Work (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - Smith, Claiborne T. - Correspondence (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - Southampton Marriages (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - Southern Churchman (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - Speeches (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Spotsylvania Records (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Stamp Covers, Postcards, etc. (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Stannard's Abstracts (All Families) (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Surry Census (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Surry Marriages (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Surry Records (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Sussex Census (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Sussex Marriages (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Sussex - Misc. Records (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - General Waller Taylor (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Taylor, Rev. Daniel II (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Tombstones and Burials - Blackstone Cemetery (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Tombstones and Burials - Blandford, 1843-1871, 1888-1943 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Tombstones and Burials - Blandford, 1872-1888 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Tombstones and Burials - Blandford (T1) (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Blandford Feild Work (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Blandford Office (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Tombstones and Burials - Fork Church (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Tombstones and Burials - Fredericksburg (Mt. Hebron) (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Tombstones and Burials - Fredericksburg (St. George's) (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Tombstones and Burials - Gloucester (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Tombstones and Burials - Hollywood (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Hollywood Book Project (Fothergill) (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Tombstones and Burials - Mt. Hebron, Winchester (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Tombstones and Burials - Norfolk (Elmwood, Cedar Grove) (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Tombstones and Burials - Norfolk (St. Paul's) (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Tombstones and Burials - Old Chapel (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Tombstones and Burials - Shockoe (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Tombstones and Burials - St. John's, Hampton (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - Tombstone Photos (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - Notebooks (18) Containing Tombstone Inscriptions from Various Cemeteries, Including Blandford, Mt. Hebron, Hollywood, and Shockoe (Box 32)
  - Tyler's Quarterly (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - UVA Records (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - VMI Material (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Gazette (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Magazine - Loose Pages (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Quarterly Extracts (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Virkus (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Warwick County Census (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Warwick County Records (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Westmoreland County (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Westmoreland County - Field Work (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Westmoreland County Notes (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - William & Mary College Records (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Virginia Colonial Abstracts - Series 2, Vol. 5 by Lindsay O. Duvall - York County, 1657-1659 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - York Marriages (Box 33, Folder 15)
- Batte Files (Box 34-36)
  The Batte files contain information on the descendants of Captain John Batte who came to Virginia from Oakwell Hall, Yorkshire, England in 1643. Included is correspondence, abstracts, source material received from other individuals, as well as various forms of a manuscript on the Batte family, which R. Bolling Batte had intended to complete and publish.
  - Correspondence - Batte (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Batte Genealogy - Correspondence - General (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - John C. Batte (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence With Mrs. Oliver B. Knight (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Batte, Olney (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - R.B. Batte I (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Thomas Batte - Explorer (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - William Batte IV (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Unconnected Members (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence - College of Arms Project (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - College of Arms Project (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Batte & Poythress Indices Since Swem (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Birstall Parish Notes (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Brunswick County Records (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Chesterfield Battes (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Misc. Notes Covering Greensville Battes (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Henrico Records, Stannard's Extracts, Charles City Records, Prince George Records - No. 1 File (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Henrico Records, Stannard's Extracts, Charles City Records, Prince George Records - No. 2 File (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Batt of Wiltshire and New England (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Oakwell Hall Prints (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Batte in Yorkshire (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Batte Family - Land (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Genealogy - Batte (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Batte Genealogy - Byrom, Henry - Correspondence, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Batte (Fothergill) (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Batte Material (Alice Ingram) (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Batte and Eppes by Mrs. Minetree (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Source Material - Batte (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Source Notes - Second Copy (Box 35, Folder 7-8)
  - Source Notes to Type (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Misc. Batte Material to be Sorted and Filed (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Misc. Batte Notes (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Misc. or Duplicate (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Prior to 1700 - Misc. Sources (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Pages for History - To Type (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Misc. Papers, Indicies, References, etc. (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Batte Manuscript (Box 36, Folder 1-3)
  - Batte Book - Extra Sheets (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Batte Manuscript - Extra Sheets (Replaced) (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Batte Manuscript - Descendants of Richard and Amy (Batte) Jones (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Batte Manuscript - 1st Revision - 15 June 1958 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Batte Manuscript - 2nd Revision - 31 August 1957 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Batte Manuscript - 3rd Revision - 11 August 1957 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Batte Manuscript - 3rd Revision - 24 September 1960 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Batte Manuscript - 4th Revision - 8 September 1957 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Batte Manuscript - 4th Revision - 15 June 1958 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Batte Manuscript - 5th Revision - 16 February 1958 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Batte Manuscript - 5th Revision - 10 September 1962 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Batte Manuscript - Greensville Branch - Fourth Copies (Box 36, Folder 15-16)
  - Batte Manuscript - Prince George - Fifth Copies (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Batte Manuscript - Prince George - Sixth Copies (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Batte Manuscript - Prince George - Seventh Set (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Batte Manuscript - Appendix A - Issue A, 16 February 1958 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Batte Manuscript - Appendix A - Issue A, 23 March 1958 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Batte Manuscript - Appendix A - Issue A, 25 May 1958 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Batte Manuscript - Appendix A - Issue A, 11 June 1958 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Batte Manuscript - Appendix A - Issue A, 1 September 1959 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Batte Manuscript - Appendix A - Issue B (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Batte Manuscript - Appendix A - Issue B, 20 April 1958 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Batte Manuscript - Appendix A - Issue B, 1 February 1961 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Batte Manuscript - Addenda (Box 36, Folder 28)
- Brodnax/Ingram Files (Box 37-41)
  The Brodnax/Ingram files were compiled by Alice Littlepage Ingram and contain correspondence, source material from other individuals, copies of court records, and information on Brodnax family homes.
  - Correspondence - Ey, Mrs. William C. (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - McGuinn, Margaret E. (Box 37, Folder 2-3)
  - Correspondence - Peck, Mrs. Lou E. (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence - Sawyer, Mildred Brodnax (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - Sawyer, Mildred Brodnax - No. 2 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence - To Mattie Ellen Trube From Alice L. Ingram (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Corrrespondence - From Mattie Ellen Trube To Alice L. Ingram (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Brodnax Notes (Box 37, Folder 9-13)
  - Genealogical Papers of Dr. John W. Brodnax (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Source Notes from Mrs. Ezell (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Source Material from Mildred E. Ezell (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Source Material from Mary Brodnax Lloyd (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Notes of John P. Madison (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Source Material from Mrs. Mattie E. Trube (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Brodnax Source Notes (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Brodnax (Box 38, Folder 8-9)
  - Brodnax/Patteson/Owen Papers (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Brodnax, Alexander (1799-1832) - (B-8)143 261 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Brodnax, Anne Walker (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Brodnax, Crowell (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Brodnax, David Walker M.D. (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Brodnax, Capt. Edward of Charles City - (B-8)143-3 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Brodnax, Edward Brooking (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Brodnax, Edward Travis M.D. - (B-8)143 265 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Brodnax, Henry (B-8)143 32 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Brodnax, Henry Powell (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Brodnax, Henry Power (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Brodnax, James (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Brodnax, John (B-8)143 23 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Brodnax, Maj. John (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Brodnax, John of Henrico and Williamsburg - (B-8)142 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Brodnax, John Belfield (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Brodnax, John Grammer M.D. (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Brodnax, John Hunt (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Brodnax, Maj. John Hunt (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Brodnax, John P. (143 283) (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Brodnax, John Travis (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Brodnax, John Wilkins M.D. (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Brodnax, John Wilson (B-8)143 261 2 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Brodnax, Meriwether Bathurst (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Brodnax, Robert (B-8) 14 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Brodnax, Robert "of Cascade" (B-8)143 261 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Brodnax, Robert M. (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Brodnax, Robert Walker M.D. (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Brodnax, Robert Withers (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Brodnax, Stephen Edward (B-8)143 37 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Edward Line - Stephen Edward Brodnax (Box 39, Folder 23-24)
  - Brodnax, Stephen Edward (Marion J. Brodnax) (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - Brodnax, Stephen Edward (Judge C.B. Pearce) (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - Brodnax, Thomas Hall (B-8)143 28 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Brodnax, William (Box 40, Folder 2-3)
  - Brodnax, William I (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Brodnax, William II (B-8)143 2 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Brodnax, William Edward of Brunswick (143 26) (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Brodnax, William Henry (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Brodnax Family (Z-25) (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Brooking I (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Brooking II (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Dalton, Amy Brodnax (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Maclin (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Munford, Robert of Amelia (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Pace-Brodnax-Knowles (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Whitaker - Mildred Brodnax Sawyer (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Wilkins (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Wilson (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Chawton Manor, Coat of Arms, etc. (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Brodnax Homes - "Cascade" - Rockingham County, NC (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Brodnax Homes - "Woodlands" - Brunswick County (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Brodnax - Marriage Records (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Brodnax Marriages (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Misc. Printed Material (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Portraits (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Wills, Deeds, Obituaries (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Misc. Records, Pedigrees, Histories, Tombstones (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Ingram - Brunswick County (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Ingram, Col. Daniel Taylor (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Ingram, Eleanor (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Ingram, John of Brunswick (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Ingram, John Littlepage (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Ingram, Joshua Rush - Campbell County (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Ingram, Lawrence M.D. (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Ingram, Page Waller (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Ingram, Samuel (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Ingram, Samuel of Lunenburg (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Ingram, Stuart Hansford (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Ingram, Lt. Sylvanus Littlepage (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Ingram Family - Loose Leaves Supplementing Red Book (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Ingram Homes - Locust Grove, Laurel Hill (Lunenburg Co.) (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Ingram - Miscellaneous (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Ingram - Various (Box 41, Folder 22)
- Epes/Eppes Files (Box 42-45)
  The Epes/Eppes files document R. Bolling Batte's interest in the ancestors of Francis Epes I. They include court record copies and abstracts, Bible records, correspondence, trial charts, clippings, source notes from other individuals, and other information concerning Batte's membership in the Epes Society.
  - "Ancestors in England of Francis Epes I of Virginia" (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence to Epes Society Containing Lineage (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Descendants of Francis Eppes Chart - Index to Surnames Not Eppes (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Diary of Dr. Richard Eppes (Copy from Alderman Library) (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Eppes (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Epes/Eppes - 11 (Box 42, Folder 6-7)
  - Epes Chart - Replaced Sheets (111-115) (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Epes/Eppes -121 (Box 42, Folder 9-10)
  - Epes/Eppes - 122 (Box 42, Folder 11-12)
  - Epes/Eppes - 123 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Epes/Eppes - 124, 132 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Epes Chart - Replaced Sheets (124) (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Epes/Eppes - No. 1 Copy (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Epes/Eppes - No. 2 File (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Epes/Eppes - No. 3 File (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Epes - ABF Notes (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Eppes Family - Amelia County Records (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Eppes - Bibles (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Eppes - Blandford Cemetery (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Epes Book (Box 43, Folder 10)